Finding Aid for the Estelle Ansley Worrell Collection
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- Patterns - (163) - Drawings - Collars, Kerchiefs, and Shawls, continued (Box 1, Folder 20, Item 3)
- Patterns - (164) - Drawings - Collars, Kerchiefs, and Shawls, continued (Box 1, Folder 20, Item 4)
- Patterns - (166) - Drawings - Draping the Skirt (Box 1, Folder 20, Item 5)
- Patterns - (167) - Drawings - Draping the Skirt, continued (Box 1, Folder 20, Item 6)
- Patterns - (169) - Drawings - The Bodice (Box 1, Folder 20, Item 7)
- Patterns - (170) - Drawings - Breeches, Trousers, and Leggings (Box 1, Folder 20, Item 8)
- Patterns - (171) - Drawings - Breeches, Trousers, and Leggings, continued (Box 1, Folder 20, Item 9)
- Patterns - (173) - Drawings - Sleeves (Box 1, Folder 20, Item 10)
- Patterns - (174) - Drawings - Sleeves, continued (Box 1, Folder 20, Item 11)
- Patterns - (175) - Drawings - Men’s Coats (Box 1, Folder 20, Item 12)
- Patterns - (177) - Drawings - Hats and Bonnets (Box 1, Folder 20, Item 13)
- Patterns - Manuscript - Armor (Box 1, Folder 20, Item 14)
- Patterns - Drawings - Armor (Box 1, Folder 20, Item 15)
- Patterns - Drawings - Armor (Box 1, Folder 20, Item 16)
- Pencil Drawings - 1770s - Family (Box 1, Folder 21, Item 1)
- Pencil Drawings - (184) - 1810 - Gentleman (Box 1, Folder 21, Item 2)
- Pencil Drawings - Couple (Box 1, Folder 21, Item 3)
- Pencil Drawings - Gentleman (Box 1, Folder 21, Item 4)
- Pencil Drawings - (145) - 1820s, 1830s, 1840s - Working Man (Box 1, Folder 21, Item 5)
- Pencil Drawings - (126) - 1810s - Gentleman (Box 1, Folder 21, Item 6)
- Pencil Drawings - (60) - 1700s, 1710s - Iroquois (Box 1, Folder 21, Item 7)
- Book Jackets - Van Nostrand Reinhold Publishers (Box 1, Folder 22, Item 1)
- Book Jackets - Stackpole Books Publishers (Box 1, Folder 22, Item 2)